<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Settersten Family</title>
    <link>https://thesetterstens.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Settersten Family</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thesetterstens.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Our Family</title>
      <link>https://thesetterstens.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesetterstens.com/about/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re a family on mission for Christ and the building of his church.
We love the outdoors, music of all kinds, good books, and exploring the wide world of trees, birds, flowers, and bugs with our little ones as we drink in the Creator&#39;s vivid brushstrokes painted across our earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2019 Update</title>
      <link>https://thesetterstens.com/posts/march_2019_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesetterstens.com/posts/march_2019_update/</guid>
      <description>Hello friends! Another winter is nearly behind us and the smells and sounds of spring are increasing every day. We&#39;re all enjoying the emerging birdsong and the kids are eager to get outside as they see the hills of snow finally melt away. Our recently started small group that meets in our home has grown now to include two other families and we&#39;re expectant of new life in community to come as much as the new life we see being born outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2018 Update</title>
      <link>https://thesetterstens.com/posts/october_2018_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesetterstens.com/posts/october_2018_update/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone!
It&#39;s hard to believe that Heather and I (Noah) and the kids have been in the Twin Cities now for almost half a year. After so long, we thought it would be encouraging to send along an update on how we&#39;re doing and what we&#39;ve been up to. Even though we&#39;re out of state, we can at least not be fully out of mind (to misappropriate an idiom).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>